[
    {
        "question": "Könyv",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Book"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pulóver",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Jumper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ceruza",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Pencil"
    },
    {
        "question": "Autó",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Car"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sapka",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Süti",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cake"
    },    
    {
        "question": "Zokni",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Socks"
    },   
     {
        "question": "Toll",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Pen"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Táska",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Bag"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Fogkefe",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Toothbrush"
    },  
    {
        "question": "Póló",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "T-shirt"
    },    
    {
        "question": "Hajkefe",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hairbrush"
    },    
    {
        "question": "Gitár",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Guitar"
    },    
    {
        "question": "Lufi",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Baloon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Törölkoző",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Towel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tolltartó",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Pencilcase"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kutya",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Dog"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vonat",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Train"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cipő",
        "answers": [ "Bag", "Baloon", "Book", "Cake", "Car", "Cat", "Dog", "Guitar", "Hairbrush", "Hat" , "Jumper", "Pen", "Pencil",  "Pencilcase",  "Shoes", "Socks", "T-shirt", "Toothbrush", "Towel", "Train" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Shoes"
    },

    {
        "question": "Egér",
        "answers": [ "Cat", "Dog", "Mouse", "Black jaguar" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mouse"
    },
    {
        "question": "Krokodil",
        "answers": [ "Cat", "Dog", "Crocodile","Mouse", "Black jaguar" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Oroszlán",
        "answers": [ "Cat", "Monkey", "Tiger",  "Zebra",  "Snake",  "Lion", "Crocodile","Mouse", "Black jaguar" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Lion"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fekete párduc",
        "answers": [ "Cat", "Monkey", "Tiger",  "Zebra",  "Snake",  "Lion", "Crocodile","Mouse", "Black jaguar" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Black jaguar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Majom",
        "answers": [ "Cat", "Monkey", "Tiger",  "Zebra",  "Snake",  "Lion", "Crocodile","Mouse", "Black jaguar" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Monkey"
    },

    {
        "question": "Tanár",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Teacher"
    },
    {
        "question": "Szék",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Chair"
    },
    {
        "question": "Asztal",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Table"
    },
    {
        "question": "Óra",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Clock"
    },
    {
        "question": "Piros",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zöld",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Green"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kék",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "Narancssárga",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Orange"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sárga",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Yellow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rózsaszín",
        "answers": [ "Teacher", "Chair", "Table",  "Clock",  "Red",  "Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Pink" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Pink"
    }

]